Wang Qian

qianwwq@qq.com

13658431688

18083024181

Student
Chongqing, China

SUMMARY

Major in English. Got TEM-4, English teacher certificate, CET-6 and NCRE Certification, Rank 2(Office). About two years of teaching experience as a homework tutor and English teacher in the English training institution. Four years of management experience as the class commissary in charge of studies. Six months of learning HTML, CSS, Typora etc.

WORK EXPERIENCE

English teacher

Donfang YiXiaoTraining institution, Nan'an District, Chongqing

Mar 2018 - Dec 2018

Worked as an English teacher, wrote the teaching plan according to New Concept English, taught students the basic grammar; two-thirds of students got 90 in the final examination.

homework tutor

ShuRen Education, Nan'an District, Chongqing

Mar 2017 - Oct 2017

Worked as a homework tutor, and in charge of answering students' questions with patience, communicating with parents in time, and working with parents to promote the healthy growth of students;

EDUCATION

Major in English

Chongqing University of Education, Nan'an District, Chongqing

2016 - Current

GPA: 3.45

Related courses:

Academic Writing, Comprehensive English, English Translation, Language Techniques

Awards

Obtained National Encouragement scholarship three times, Obtained first-class scholarship five times, Obtained the title of outstanding three-good student twice,

ABILITY

Teaching

Two years of teaching experience, familiar with students' study habits and junior high school English textbook.

Writing

Won the first prize in the PiGai Cup writing competition at the municipal level in 2017 and third prize in the Chongqing Nade Cup English Document writing competition. Six months of learning academic writing.

Managing

Worked as the class commissary in charge of studies, good at managing the class and maintaining the classroom discipline.